Hello and welcome to the Junkyard Love.
>> Hey, everything's going to be all right.
>> It's all good. It's all good.
>> The Junkyard Love podcast.
the junkyard. Okay, one. Dude, let's
start right here. Um, good morning, man.
Trey, thank you again. Welcome to the
podcast. Uh, let's have some fun, man. I
want to start with right there. You just
told me you're drinking some bone broth
that you made at home. You were texting
me and you told me that you had like a
morning routine, basically. Do you want
to start with your morning routine? Like
I think anybody listening would probably
benefit from hearing kind of how you
live your life in the mornings ideally.
>> Yeah, most definitely. And uh thank you
again for bringing me on here. You know,
this is a huge opportunity for me. I've
been praying and asking for God for a
platform, you know, since two months
ago,
and here it is. So, but yeah, let's
delve into it. My uh my rising ritual is
what I call it. uh consists of waking up
around 5 6 a.m. It's kind of loose. It's
not like I don't wake up with an alarm.
It's just whenever I rise and I jump
immediately into meditation. And during
my meditation, I I kind of picture who I
envision myself to be. And then I work
through it, you know, like what it feels
like, what it what it's going to consist
of full spectrum. And then I let go and
that's when I go into like more of a
transcendental type meditation. And I
just kind of float just float through
it. And I always finish in gratitude,
but I always do my gratitude a little
different. I instead of saying like in
my head like I'm grateful for this or
I'm grateful for that, I just picture
all the good things that I have going on
in my life and I hold the energy of
gratitude. So it's more of like a like a
fast-paced slideshow more than, you
know, me just listing things that I'm
grateful for. And then after my
gratitude and meditation and everything,
I jump straight into some sort of
movement. I call it my mobility
exercises and I take every single one of
my joints, muscles, and ligaments
through its full range of motion
multiple times. And kind of just wakes
the body up. And then I go into if I
don't work out, I'll just jump straight
into a shower and finish cold. Always
cold finish, you know, because I don't
have a cold plunge yet. Soon as I get a
cold plunge, it's game on, you know. I'm
going to live in that thing. But uh
>> I need one too, dude. I need one, too.
>> Oh, I know. But as soon as I tried it, I
was like, I need one of these, you know?
>> Yeah. I'll do the bathtub once in a
while, but it just doesn't hit the same.
>> No, you got to embrace the suck. And it
doesn't suck quite as much in the
shower, you know?
>> Mhm.
>> But then after I finish the meditation,
I I get right into it and I'm normally
up um with something healthy for
breakfast. I'll jump with like two eggs,
you know, two eggs and a piece of toast
or bone broth. And like today I had the
bone broth and we get our bones straight
from the butcher. So, well, not even a
butcher, it's just a farmer that
butchers and we just boil them
overnight,
you know. So, we have it the bones get
like jelly, you know, by the time that
they're done boiling, you know,
>> right?
>> And I just add like some super
mineralized salt to it and that's
breakfast.
>> Hell yeah. Yeah. And then you're ready
to rock and roll. That's that's like an
ideal morning for you right there.
>> Yeah. I found that the more that I eat
for breakfast, the the lazier I am, you
know.
>> Word. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, I try to stay full, stay
hungry, stay motivated, and stay
energetic, you know.
>> Yeah. Do you find benefit from kind of
waking up and not immediately eating
breakfast? Because that's how I am.
>> Yeah. Yeah, definitely. If I wake up and
I immediately eat, then I find myself
scrolling instead of like posting or
creating content or, you know, replying
to people with something meaningful as
opposed to just getting on Instagram and
scrolling and wasting time.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I think there's something
good to be said about the where you
allow your levels of consumption to roam
like first thing in the morning. You
know, we all know the feeling of we do,
you know, lean over and scroll or
something and then we just go, I wish I
didn't do that. you know, uh, and then
on the offside.
>> Yeah, it's like we we just have to
repeat the same lesson for some reason.
But, um, yeah, it's good to have that
mental diet in the morning as well as
that as that physical diet. Um, and then
also not eating, you know, complete
garbage is as as best you can. You know,
it's like you live your life once in a
while, but try not to eat total garbage
first thing in the morning. It's just
harder to have a, you know, a soft
mental day throughout the rest of the
day.
>> Yeah. I was actually talking to somebody
about that just last night.
um he was going through this depression
phase, you know, he's like, "Oh, I like
woe is me." You know, the victim
mentality, you know, what I preach about
on my Insta.
>> He um he's just talking about everything
negative, you know. And I'm I'm telling
him like this is confirmation bias. The
like what you see, what you focus on is
what you're going to see and and what
grows essentially, you know. And it
starts with what you put into your
engine. You know, if your body is an
engine, what kind of fuel are you giving
it? And he's telling me he goes to like
Burger King every day after work and,
you know, eats McDonald's and Happy
Meals or whatever it is, you know. And
I'm like, think about that, bro. Like,
you are literally putting garbage into
your body and you're expecting a a high
output human being to be the product of
that.
>> Mhm.
>> Not likely.
>> Yeah. It's like um
Yeah. like we like it's our fuel
resource, you know, like if you put old
crappy oil in your car, it's not going
to run as good as like some healthy
healthy good oil, you know what I mean?
>> Um, and it's also I think there's
something to be said about
like the obviously all the preservatives
and all of those things, but kind of
just like the energetics of of too much
fast food. Um, I think there's something
to be said about like someone who's
isn't incredibly happy with what's going
on in their life. Um, like what they
might put into your food. Not that
everybody who works at fast food is, you
know, unhappy. That's not what I'm like
entirely insinuating. But um sometimes I
I feel that
food is this sacred thing. Like we have
been um Ramina Maharshi who is Ramdas's
guru uh like like two of the huge things
that he would always say to Ramdas is is
Ramdas um feed people and love everyone.
And like that was always Ramas would
always just go through like how he would
how would he do those things and like he
also feed people and there was all these
mystical stories about these gurus who
would like find ways through their
spiritual way of of like there's only a
tiny amount of soup in this bowl but we
have to serve 50 people but somehow if
you just believe in this guru and you
just keep serving people you will just
just don't look at the ladle soup will
still come and you'll feed all these
people and that'll be a bottomless thing
of soup. So, I don't know. I I just feel
like there is a connection to us through
the years and years of communities and
and um just being humans. Uh when it
comes to serving food, when it comes to
like like you're giving someone
nutrients in life, how many days can we
really go without, you know, without
nutrients, without food? It's like who
we are. And so,
>> that's interesting, too.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Isn't it? I I just think
like there might be some subperceptual
effect in some way on someone
dissatisfyingly serving you what we call
food and it's really like preservatives
and garbage and stuff that doesn't make
you feel good. It's it's mouthpleasure
for the sake of like non-nutrients long
term. So I don't know.
>> Yeah, I just seen something about Oreos
that obviously Oreos are garbage, but
it's apparently they're 85%
preservatives. 85% like what is the
other 15% though you know?
>> Yeah. And uh another thing on food, I
seen this guy who um the longest
recorded fast in history, he went 385
days without food,
>> dude. 300. And he cured every disease
that he had in his body, you know, like
like I've fasted, don't get me wrong.
I've gone the longest I've gone was uh
like 40 40 days without food. And
>> dude, dick.
>> And that was a struggle. And there was
like it wasn't I was having liquid. So,
I mean, I was having like water and
stuff, but um in between that I was
going days where I was just dry fasting
as well. And the dry fasting is that's a
mental game, you know, cuz if you have
water, you're like, "Oh, at least I have
this to rely on. I could just drink a
bunch of water. I feel full, you know,
but then when you have those those dry
fasting days, it really gets mental, you
know, and it
>> it really breaks you down, you know."
>> Yeah. Yeah. Is it do you ever get I
think the the thing with me when I try
to do a long fast is I get to this weird
point where fear kind of wins and I go I
think maybe this is a bad feeling. I I
basically because you're analyzing how
you feel and you're like is does is my
stomach acting weird and my skin is
being this and what you know there's a
lot of changes going on and so I think
when I throw in the towel earlier than I
had originally wanted to it's usually
because
>> my body is saying like there's something
wrong or like this headache is a really
bad headache and you should really eat
and then and then I gave it. Do you
experience anything like that? Is that
part of your mental game? Like you got
to just not listen to those voices?
>> Yeah, 100%. That's psychossematic
self-destruction is what it is, you
know, and you're you're going to be
your, you know, your best friend or your
worst enemy when it comes to a fast
because you can psych yourself in or out
of any situation. Think about anything
you do in life. Like when it comes to
even a podcast, your first one, your
nerves probably got you. Your nerves
were like, "Oh man, I'm going to
misspeak or I'm going to do this on on
camera and you know, people aren't going
to like my podcast or people aren't
going to like me." But then on the flip
side of that, if you're like, "Oh, I'm
the [__] Like, I don't give a [__] what
anybody thinks that. Like, everyone's
going to love me because I love me. I'm
awesome." You know? And the same thing
goes with your food and your fasting. If
you believe that you can do 40 days,
then you're going to do 40 days. The
only reason that you wouldn't be able to
do those 40 days is because of
self-doubt.
>> Okay? So, so say someone is on that,
they're about to go on 40 days or
whatever their version of 40 days is.
Maybe it's two days, whatever. And they
have this initial start point. They're
like, "I believe." And it's true. And
they believe it. And they're like,
"Dude, I'm in. Like, seriously, I'm
doing this. There's no way I'm not." And
then they get to hour 36. They're going
to go 48. And then they get that voice.
Like, what how do you how do you bridge
the gap between who chose to set out on
that journey and who you are like right
now, 36 hours in, who's just feeling
like they're getting their ass kicked?
What do you have to say
>> that? It comes down to willpower. You
know, you got to have the the willpower,
your willpower is a muscle essentially.
And the more that you exercise it, the
stronger it is. So, if you go if you
refrain from eating fast food for a
week, the next week is going to be a
little bit easier and so on and so
forth. So, if 48 hours is too hard for
you for a fast, start with 72 and or
start with, you know, 24 hours, then
work your way to 48, then go to 72. You
know, you just got to strengthen that
willpower and then eventually your mind
is going to be your biggest advocate.
>> Yeah. Yeah, dude. I I mean, I that's so
perfect because when it comes to
meditation, that's the that's the thing
that I'm always saying as well is Yeah.
Maybe when you sit down, you're going to
go, "Dude, my mind is chaos and I'm just
too ADHD and I can't personally meditate
and my brain specifically out of all the
other 8 billion people on the planet is
like can't it can't meditate and just
all the things, you know." Um, but
comparing it to going to the gym and
like, bro, you don't walk into the gym
and just lift up a 50 pounder and start
curling it, you know? You got to go
every day and you start with the fives
and then you go to the tens and the 15s
and then 12.5s if you if the 15s feel
too heavy, you know, and every day
you're building that. It's like we it's
it's interesting because so we have the
brain, we have all of our organs, you
know, your heart's a muscle, all of our
physical things here, and then we have
the subtle the subtle body, the mind.
Like where is the mind, you know, like
where you know what I mean? Like there's
the brain like is your mind just in your
brain? Well, no. It's like it's the
whole experience of your body. And so if
we think of part of the human experience
being, you know, that the physical body,
you can go to the gym and prove all that
to yourself in real time. Like go to the
gym, workout for 3 weeks, and you
literally are like, I'm I'm taller and I
stand up straighter and yes, my shirt is
a little bit tighter. It's it's proving
myself in real time. And the subtle
body, the mental version of our body, of
who we are, is also in need of that uh
maturation through through daily work
through the 5 lb curls like you like you
said, you know, uh showing up and
earning it, like proving to yourself,
all right, dude, I normally eat every 3
hours, but I'm going to start just I'm
going to eat for four hours or not eat
for four hours.
>> Okay, I did that. You know, I'm going to
wait 16 hours until I eat next. I've
never done that my whole life. And then
you prove to yourself that you can do
it. And then suddenly you're that new
person. You're standing as the person
who has now fasted more than 16 hours,
more than 15 hours. And so you can then
act from there. So yeah, man, it's that
uh that subtle body muscle building,
right? You got to be a subtle body
muscle builder.
>> Yeah, it kind of ties into that
expression, fake it until you make it.
You know, you got to your belief creates
your reality 100%. And I believe that
wholeheartedly and I'm kind of tie into
that, you know, with this subtle body um
perception that you have um and
meditation. So when you meditate,
obviously you have this like plethora of
ideas, thoughts, feelings, emotions just
flowing into your head simultaneously.
And in order to disassociate,
um I I actually got this from an author.
His name is Ken Wilbur. And he calls it
the witness state.
>> And the witness state is essentially
stepping back from everything physical,
emotional, and spiritual and realizing
that you are all of the above, right?
And you're just observing it. So you're
observing all these thoughts, feelings,
and emotions that flow through your
awareness. And when you're when you have
that, when you step back into this
witness state, all of a sudden, the
things that affected you no longer have
precedence or hold on your life because
they're not you. The true you is the
witness behind it all.
Yeah. You are the one that observes.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I mean, well, so how is that? I
feel like trying to put myself in the
shoes of someone who's listening who's
like never really like dove that deep on
meditation or any of those like getting
meta on your own thoughts, you know? I
think, you know, when I was in probably
my worst version of like my victim
mindset when I was depressed and all
these sorts of things at my worst, I
think that I thought I was my thoughts.
You know what I mean? So, can we talk a
little bit more about maybe we could
start with like how it first maybe
started for you, bro? like how you first
kind of started going, you know what?
Like, oh, I I can like observe my
thoughts rather than just get caught up
in them, you know? I mean, it's such a
huge opening when it comes to the
awakening path, when it comes to like
taking control of your life. So, man, I
I'd love to know how that was for you.
>> Yeah, definitely. So, for me, it started
with the awareness of
like you I was using victim mentality as
a crutch. I was using it as leverage to
get what I wanted. I was using it to
like cuz I was in prison. I spent a
decade in prison. And what little
outside interaction I did have, I
manipulated through victim mindset,
right? Victim mentality because victim
mentality is just inverted narcissism
instead of you saying like, "Oh, wo is
me." Or so like instead of like um
narcissism where you're like, "Oh, I'm
so great. You know, look at me. Look at
me." Uh victim mentality. It's like,
"Oh, look how horrible my life is. I
need you to take sympathy on me." And
then you leverage that for manipulation,
you know, like, "Oh, I need $20, you
know, so put 20 bucks on my books so
that I can get some food or, you know,
whatever the situation may be." But
instead of demanding admiration, you
demand sympathy, you know. So, I mean,
they kind of play into each other. But
for me personally, I had to recognize
that I was using victim mentality as a
crutch in the first place and realize
that I was, you know, narcissistic,
you know, like that at its root. That's
just narcissism with a different a
different hat.
>> And once I realized that I was
narcissistic and this was due to, you
know, information reading, I read a book
called uh dark psychology. And dark
psychology doesn't mean like
intrinsically evil. It can be used for
that. But it was more like neural
linguistic programming and uh
recognizing your own triggers, your own
fallacies in life. Recognizing how you
use, you know, manipulation or
narcissism to get the things in life
that you want. And because of this, I
realized like I'm messed up. Like I am
I'm a messed up individual. And because
of that, look where I am. I'm I'm
serving a 15-year sentence in a
Tennessee prison, 1500 miles away from
anyone I even know or love, and I don't
get a single letter or phone call. Like,
I am a product of my mindset at this
point.
>> And once I realized that, I started
changing my mindset one day at a time.
Every time something came into my
awareness, I was like, is this me
speaking or is this the victim version
of me speaking? And it wasn't until
I had my lowest point, like I I
literally hit rock bottom. And my rock
bottom was I overdosed in a Tennessee
prison. I was doing tattoos, you know,
one day and I'm a tattoo artist. So I'm
setting up for a tattoo. Somebody comes
in and they're like, "Hey, do you want a
little bump?" That little bump was that
was my turning point because it it was
fentanyl.
>> That fentanyl put me out. I woke up 18
minutes later, six cans in our can and
about three shocks with the paddles. And
I came too and the first thing I thought
was like everything in my life needs to
change because everything in my life up
to this point led me to this moment.
>> Wow.
>> You know, so it just starts with
recognition.
>> So, do you consider yourself do you I
mean, I'm sure you've done some some
research and come across this. Do you
think you had a near-death experience
like that like is really kind of a
turning point and that like kind of
popped you out into this new like
purpose driven?
>> Yeah, 100%. The first and first and
foremost at the time I had a son and uh
my partner um Chelsea who you met, we
were separated so he they weren't in my
life at all. The first thing I seen like
while I was gone, you know, I seen this
I seen my son and uh all I held was
regret like this is like I'm going to
die in a Tennessee prison and my son's
not going to know who I am, you know? So
I just I had this like overwhelming
sense of regret for the way that I I led
my life, you know.
And as soon as the regret faded,
something else took over. And it was
perspective.
And I all of a sudden instantaneously,
like it was literally instantaneously, I
had like an overwhelming sense of
perspective on life. Like everything
everything that came into my awareness
from that point on, I knew whether or
not it was going to serve the version of
myself that was going to move and propel
me forward in life or it was going to
keep me in stagnation.
Why do you think
why do you think you were ripe in that
moment? I know that's a weird word to
use. Um, but like what like do you think
it was, you know, I mean, I guess I'm
exploring what a rock bottom is in some
ways, but like what is it that finally
breaks the dam and gives us that that
perspective? I mean, I had a similar
experience myself.
What do you think that you know not only
brings us to be right but makes us right
for you know that time that thing that
environment?
>> I think it is a case by case basis you
know cuz each person is different.
Everybody's rock bottom is going to be
different. For me personally it took
loing my life you know because I've been
I've been through some stuff man. I I've
lived a crazy life. I was a uh street
pharmacist to put it as small as
possible.
>> I hear you.
>> Um yeah, so I was a street pharmacist
for years and I hung out with gangs. I
hung out with other street pharmacists.
I hung out with low lives, uh strippers,
I hung out with the dredges of society.
And because of that, my mindset, it
mirrored that.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You got to be what's it? You
know, there's that typical saying of
you're the product of the the five
closest people to you or whatever. And
there's some truth in that, not all
truth in that. There's
it is interesting like when you have
these sort of experiences when you have
these sort of awakenings or like
near-death experience or you have some
sort of kind of like snapping out of
your patterns your typical way of living
it does give you kind of this oh I'm in
order to even connect with these people
like yeah I love them and I appreciate
them and I've been through a lot with
them in these like this complicated way
but in order to like go where I know
damn well I need to be going cuz my
brain has been telling it to me in in
the background like every day all day.
If I really listen to that voice, I
don't know if they could come with me. I
don't know if I could keep hanging out
with them every day. I don't know that I
get to have the same relationship with
them in order to be who I know I need to
be now. And that is, you know, that's a
that's a very alienating, lonely place
to take a take a step on. You know what
I mean?
>> I mean, it can be. It can be, but it
depends on your perspective. For me
personally, my perspective on that
situation was if we are all God, right?
Like you're God, I'm God, this
microphone I'm talking into is a piece
of God, then that means that everything
that comes into your awareness is just a
perspective that God has gifted you. So
if you are alienating someone who is a
negative asset in your life, that's just
a piece of God that he gave you for that
perspective, like for a lesson. So
you're not alienating any one person.
You're just alienating an energetic
frequency that God gave you for
perspective.
>> Okay. Well, what's what's the step after
that when we notice that it's time to
move away from these different crowds,
these different times? I mean, you could
share what happened with you, but um I'm
always I'm always asking like the person
who's listening right now, I'm always
thinking about them if they're like,
"Yo, damn, dude. I kind of I think maybe
it is time to like change. I think it is
time to like I have been a victim in
some way or I have you know etc. I got
to move on. What do you think?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Definitely. I mean if you
are currently going through that
transformation phase where you're on the
precipice of you know exiling the old
you to bring in the new you. There's
going to be a lot of changes that are
happening when it comes to your
energies, your emotions, and especially
the crowd that you surround yourself
with.
>> And for me, I had to I had to just cut
ties. It wasn't like a a text message
where I was like, "Hey, bro, like I love
you, but it's no more like we can't hang
out." It was just that's it. No longer
texted, no longer called, no longer like
I spent I spent a decade locked up. So,
it was a lot easier for me to ostracize
the people that were no longer serving
the highest version that I saw myself
being.
>> It was a lot simpler because when I got
out of prison, those people that weren't
around, they stayed gone. And if they
tried to hit me up, like, where were you
then?
>> You know, where were you when I needed
you the most? you know, so I'm not I'm
not going to slip backwards into these
old energies, old frequencies or old
patterns just because someone says,
"What's up, bro?" You know?
>> Right. Right. Yeah. You don't need to
keep that um connection constantly open
if it's just no longer serving you. And
you know, it doesn't even doesn't even
have to be like, "Fuck you, bro." It's
just like, "Hey, man. I'm just I'm just
moving in a different place, you know? I
hope you I hope you move to your to your
best place,
>> you know?"
>> Yeah. And since then, I've actually had
um and it's crazy how this works. Um
I've had two or three friends who I was
really really close with, you know, back
in the day. And we've like shed blood
together, shed tears together, we've
made money together, and we've gotten
locked up together, you know, and when I
got out, I I cut ties. But here
recently, I've had a couple of them that
have hit me up and they're like, "Hey,
I'm doing really good. you know, I got
this going on in my life and blas blas
and you know what, like I'd love to
reconnect with you. I would love to see
your your story, hear your transition,
you know, because to completely
discredit someone just because of their
past would be discrediting myself,
>> you know. So, you got to give someone
the opportunity to redeem themselves if
they are truly trying to do better and
be better and succumb to the desires
that propel them in the right direction.
You can't give up on those people
because then they're going to think
subconsciously like maybe I'm not
worthy. You know,
>> cuz think about like when you were going
through your transformation phases or,
you know, quitting drinking or stop
eating fast food. If you would have had
somebody come into your awareness and
they're just like, "Oh yeah, [__] that."
Like, "I I don't believe in your
journey." It would have made you feel a
certain type of way.
>> Mhm.
>> Oh, hold on. I think my camera just
turned off.
>> Yeah, I was wondering as as soon as it
did that, I thought that it might I
think I can still hear you, though. I'm
not sure what what we were talking
about, but uh Hey, how about this? Let's
pick up where. Um,
all right, Trey. So, your Instagram
handle is from prison to purpose. What
is your purpose?
>> My purpose now in life is to offer the
same perspectives that I went through so
that people don't have to go through the
same struggles that I did because I
don't want people to have to reach the
same levels of rock bottom to have the
perspective that I achieved. You know, I
don't believe that everyone has to die
to find their true self.
>> What What is it in you that
and and I asked this as, you know,
knowing that there's something within me
that does the same thing. What is it
that's within us, I guess, that
can't help like we can't help us share
and want to help people, you know, like
it's not just I don't want to heal and
just selfishly keep it to myself and
just be on an island. like I have this
hunger for giving what I've learned and
in that same boat, you know, not wanting
to see other people fail where I failed
and like hopefully, you know, share my
perspective, that sort of thing. What
what is that within you, you know?
>> Um, to put it simply, it's it's God,
man. It's God. Like if we are all God,
we're all just trying to pick different
versions of ourselves up because we're
all a little piece of the puzzle, you
know, and without each piece being
brought up together, you know, we all
fall.
>> Okay. How long have you had a a
perspective on God? Has this been a
lifetime or is this like did this happen
after kind of your your overdose
experience?
>> Um, I mean, a little bit of both. I I
don't see God like like a Christian God.
It's not like the Bible God, you know? I
see God as like an energy, a frequency,
an awareness, a consciousness. Like God
is everything and all that is and all
that ever was, you know, time and
memorial and so on and so forth. And
that perspective kind of came through
just years and years of meditation and
introspection and realizing that like
it's all connected like everything like
the energy that flows through me flows
through you that flows through you know
each blade of grass you know and not
only that but like our awareness and our
consciousness has a direct effect on
every single thing within our awareness
you know. Have you seen the Here's a
little caveat. So, have you heard of the
double slit experiment?
>> I mean, explain it for explain it for
those who haven't heard.
>> Yeah. So, the double slit experiment is
simply put, you have a particle, right?
You have a what was it? Electron an
electron particle being shot through uh
two slits on and my camera's off again.
Is it electro? Bro, blow. Bro, you
observed the particle.
>> I know, right?
>> Okay, brother. So, we were talking about
um we're talking about your purpose just
a second ago. So,
how has you know trying to live through
your purpose or you know, maybe not even
trying but actively living through your
purpose as just kind of who you are. you
know, it's like seems like your identity
comes from that rather than you trying
to like have this identity. How how has
that changed your life? How's that
shaped kind of your dayto-day the way
you were versus the way you are now?
>> Well, I I'm going to answer that with a
story.
>> So,
uh about two years ago, I was I was
roofing, right? And I didn't like it
obviously. It just it felt like it was
at a stark contrast for who I I felt
like I should be. But it was an income,
you know, I wasn't relying on anything
other than my manual labor to
to bring in an income in for my family
to, you know, provide for my family. And
one day I I cut my thumb and it was
pretty bad. It wasn't like
life-threatening or anything like that,
but it was bad enough to the point where
I had to take time off work, you know, I
wasn't going to be able to work from it.
I cut it to the bone, you know, and it
like literally instantaneously as soon
as it happened though, it was like I'm
done. Like that not just with roofing
but with manual labor altogether. Like
this does not serve my soul, you know?
And
it was from that moment on that I
pursued
uh social media. Like if it wasn't for
me hurting my thumb and then
subsequently uh I tore a bunch of
ligaments in my shoulder because I was
riding a onehe. And those two things
together made me realize that like my
body is is temporary, but my mind can
last a lifetime if I put it out there.
And so I started I started putting
myself out there through social media
and I started just kind of being myself,
you know, you know, kind of goofy and
zany. And I didn't really have a
direction or a purpose or anything like
that. I was just, you know, getting
online and posting. And it wasn't until
recently that I realized that like I
needed direction. Like I needed I needed
like real purpose.
And
because of that, I found I found victim
mentality and well, it found me, you
know, and I took my own story, my own
healing, my own traumas that I went
through and I turned them into I turned
them into purpose, you know, like my
name implies, you know, prison to
purpose. And prison isn't just like a
physical place. It's it's a mindset. And
if you have if you have a mindset of a
prisoner, you're gonna always be a
prisoner, whether it be in a physical
prison or you inside your own home. and
overcoming that has been has been a
journey, you know, and I'm grateful to
be on it and I'm every day I wake up
just just blessed that I have an
opportunity to speak and I have so many
people that reach out to me and that are
thankful for offering, you know, these
perspectives and I just hope and pray
that, you know, I can help help people
before they have to reach the level of
rock bottom that I did.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I I love that you listened
to that intuitive voice that was like,
yo, I can work with my hands. I can do
this, but I actually have this thing
that's burning brighter within me and I
need to use my words. I need to use my
intellect. I need to I need to do
something different because I have
something worth giving that other people
are are needing to receive. So, uh, hell
yeah for for following that voice, man.
And and I'm glad you did. So, I want to
talk more about victim mentality. I
don't want to get totally caught up in
just talking about men masculine victim
mentality, but I do want to zoom in on
just that for a second. Can you give me
like because I'm always, you know, like
I said, I'm always thinking about the
listener. Uh, you know, they're on right
on the edge. Maybe they're kind of
discovering through this conversation
that they've been a little bit more on
the victim side of or totally on the
victim side or uh you know maybe they're
they're a young man who realizes that
the way that they learned how to
perceive themselves and like interact
with the world maybe from their parents
or their environment whatever is kind of
the victim stuff and they now need to
start learning about it. They need to
move forward. Um so thinking about men
specifically I guess where where would
we start?
Well, it it definitely starts in the
mind. You got to realize that you have
victim mentality in the first place
because if you don't even know that you
will have victim mentality, you're never
going to be able to heal from it. You
know, your pain explains behavior, but
it does not excuse it. Healing isn't
being like understood. Healing is
becoming someone that your past can no
longer control.
So I guess in short it just it starts
with it starts with realizing that you
have fallacies. You have room to grow.
You know nobody's perfect and in fact
nobody's perfect you know like emphasis
on nobody. We all have room to grow. We
all have learned um we all have room to
learn and things that we can pick up
from others you know and that's exactly
why we're here. kind of like a segue
into our past conversation like we reach
down and pull people up because we're
all a piece of God, you know?
>> Yeah. We're we're all just I say this
like every podcast episode because I'm
corny, but uh Ram Das says we're all
just walking each other home, you know?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. And like you said, Ramdas says uh
feed everyone. And you know, like who
says he's even talking about food?
>> Exactly. Yep. Yeah. Yeah. Like if you
have something that is nutrientdense for
a for another human being then like I'm
thinking of Terence McKenna has that
that thing nature loves courage. It's
like even when it comes to feeding one
another, even when it comes to serving
one another or whatever that version of
it is for you, it's like nature like
you're not doing it for the reward. Of
course not. But it does it's it's juicy
and it's ripe. You know, nature almost
rewards you because it gives you
perspective and it and it makes you go
like, man, I'm glad that I was, you
know, in that position to give that
person that bit of knowledge. I'm glad
that like I was able to genuinely help
them when they needed some help. like
that's, you know, no, I'm not doing this
for me, but hey, that does feel pretty
good, you know, that's that's a good
thing. It actually makes me want to do
it again. It makes me want to serve more
people, in fact, you know.
>> Mhm. And I mean, to get to get into
that, to add to that, it is actually a
little bit selfish, you know, because
you get a little bit of a dopamine boost
when you reach down and you help
somebody. It makes you feel good. So
when you continuously do that and you're
continuously reaching down to help
people and pick people up like it is a
little bit selfish because you get just
as much from it as they do.
>> So do you think that's a so do you think
that's a bad thing? Do you think that it
is? I mean, so Ramdas also talks about
how he would turn himself he would
always be wary of not turning himself
into the helper. Like if I'm the helper,
you have I have to turn you into the
person who needs help and then I'm kind
of looking down on you as the person who
has the answers you need, you know?
>> Yeah, it can be. It definitely can be.
If you if you identify as a person who
is always helping people and and it's a
self-s serve, like your purpose is self-
serving. you're helping people so that
you can feel good, then all of a sudden
that help is demonized.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's like it um
I don't know. It's like um it's kind of
like coming across needy almost like I
need you to reaffirm who I am, you know?
It's like, man, that's you know, you you
get that experience sometimes just
naturally, but you don't you don't you
aren't owed the reaffirmation of who you
think you are with every interaction.
I'm like, come on, dude.
>> Yeah. Yeah, 100%. Um, I have this little
quote here.
>> Um, I I don't know who wrote this, but
it it's uh healing culture taught people
how to feel. It forgot to teach them how
to become.
>> Okay. What does that mean to you? What
what's what's the difference between
healing and becoming?
>> So, healing culture taught people how to
feel. So essentially
it taught people how to feel better,
right? But it didn't teach them how to
be better. So being better is a mindset,
but feeling better is just that. It's
just a feeling, you know? So healing
culture is just temporary. Like when you
watch motivational videos, you get all
motivated and you get pumped up and you
get like energetic maybe for a workout
or something like that, but it's it's
not your baseline. It's not your
default.
It's it's not making you become
motivated. That comes from consistent
action that comes from an identity. So
in order to heal like victim mentality
or to heal like whatever you've gone
through, you need to change the identity
that is your baseline.
>> Okay, let's dig deeper into identity
because I agree. I think that's one of
the most important things. Uh what can
you tell me what what can you tell me
that you discovered about identity
through your through your process here?
>> I would say that
identity is it's your subconscious
beliefs on who you are, right? So, if
you are consistently
hanging around people that affirm an old
identity of you, like say you hang
around a bunch of people back in your
party days and they're like, "Oh, bro,
you're such a party animal, man. You can
drink so much and you can do this and
this and that." Like, they're affirming
an identity that maybe you don't hold
true to yourself anymore,
>> you know? So, you got to surround
yourself with people that believe in the
identity that you believe in,
>> you know?
>> Yeah, dude. I I think I it's fresh in my
mind because like I just visited my
hometown and that's always a um
I mean I I hate talking about like my
hometown like it's like I'm think I'm
better than it or something but there is
just a lot of those conversations that
happen or like bro oh you remember when
you they like have an inside joke from
you know 16 years ago which is beautiful
in a lot of aspects but when it's some
sort of like oh dude you were keg
standing on the party in the you know
like just some crazy story that you had.
It's like, man, I don't even I don't
remember that. Like, it doesn't really
feel like me. Like, if you bring that up
and you think that that correlates to
who I am now, it kind of makes me feel
like you don't really see who I am now,
which makes me feel a little small,
>> you know? And so, it's uh it's it is
kind of a journey of interacting with uh
people who you want to love and interact
with, but they're only holding on to
older versions of you, right,
>> bro? Yes. Yes. 100%. I vibe with
everything you just said right there. I
went and seen like my family and I do
not see my family very often like for
that reason specifically because they
are consistently trying to affirm an old
identity that no longer serves me. You
know, especially my dad. My dad is so
just
stubborn. Like it's it's like talking to
a brick wall, you know? Every time I'm
telling him like, "Oh, like this is what
I have going on in my life." He's like,
"Yeah, but is it [__] paying the
bills? Is it doing this or that? Like
it's my passion, you know, that doesn't
mean anything to him.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, so it's it's hard to explain
an identity to a rock.
>> Yeah. Uh, I mean, it's I I I think it's
like a lot of it is it must be as a
parent, it must be like weird if you
feel a type of way and you're not super
aware of like what it feels like when
you know, your son is maybe doing
something that you wish you did or maybe
like like you know, you probably heard
of like um when you know a a kid starts
making more money at a certain point in
their life than their parents ever did.
you know, there's of course gonna be a
lot of like natural pride, but then
there's also this kind of strange like,
oh, like you did better than me or it
kind of like forces this sort of I think
it kind of does trigger something when
someone is like um I think it's the same
thing that's triggered when I'm just
trying to eat healthy next to someone
and they are offended or they like
insult themselves off of the whatever
they're eating just because I'm eating
healthy next to them. I'm like, "Buddy,
I'm not trying to
>> You don't have to compare what you have
going on to what I have going on. I'm
not trying to trigger you to like do
anything differently, but like,
can I have this thing over here?" You
know, you can have your thing, but can I
have my thing over here? When it comes
to a parent relationship, it's like,
can't you be at least a little happy
that I have this thing over here that
I'm clearly excited about? You know,
>> yeah. The way the way that I look at it
so that I don't find myself feeling some
type of way when people like pass
judgment is the expression I don't know
who it's from but you will never be
judged by somebody doing less than you
or by somebody doing more than you. You
will never be judged by somebody doing
more than you.
>> You know so judgment always comes from
somebody from a lower position in life
that are casting judgment because they
feel a certain way towards you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It makes me think of that.
You ever hear that thing about um uh
basically like Kobe Bryant is never
going to be typing a comment on
someone's social media post, you know?
He's never going to be like judging
someone or like talking [__] on a post
or like he's never going to be on Reddit
just like insulting someone cuz he's
just he's like why would he ever think
like that? Why would he ever waste his
time?
>> Yeah. If somebody's like, "Oh, Jordan's
the best player that ever lived." You're
not going to see Kobe in the comments be
like, "No, I am."
>> Yeah. No, he's going to go prove it by
being out on the court.
>> Yeah, exactly.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Uh well, I mean, we get
caught up in
we get caught up in our identities, you
know what I mean? So, uh I want to talk
more about identity. What I mean,
clearly you've spent time in prison. I
mean, I'm sure you probably were around
a lot of people who were caught in an
identity of victimhood, not some version
of this thing happened to me. I grew up
in this experience. That's why I am this
way and therefore I cannot change
because genetics, you know, or um
there's, you know, they don't even think
that there's a, you know, a way out. So,
what did you see a lot and I guess what
would be
I don't know like what what what would
you have to offer them now now that
you're on a different perspective
yourself like maybe you know I give you
a microphone tray and you're kind of
like talking to a room full of people
that you used to be in rooms with you
know 9 8 n years ago what what could you
offer them
>> well probably about the same amount that
I was able to offer them then um not
much because people in there are not
open to the ideas that we're discussing.
You know, it takes a certain type of
person that is ready for advancement in
life and ready to change the identity
that they possess. I was surrounded I
was in a maximum security prison in
Tennessee. I was surrounded by murderers
and drug dealers, rapists, and the
literally the worst of society over
there. And I was right outside of
Memphis, which is like the murder
capital of the world right now. And it
was it was the wild west. Like it's not
a point of pride or anything. Like I
literally had to sleep with a a handmade
knife in my cell every night for fear of
my own life,
>> you know? And it's
and when I was in there and I did talk
to people on any sort of philosophical
level, it either went right over their
head or they were offended. They were
offended because they felt like I was
trying to make them feel dumb.
>> And like I don't I don't talk like I'm
some super genius. I don't talk like I'm
some doctor or whatever, you know? I
don't have a college degree. And it's
just the people in there and their
mentality is so stuck in their ways. You
know, it's it's gang mentality. It's
prison mentality. It's victim mentality
at its finest. And you can't convince
somebody to change their life. You can
you can never convince somebody to
change their life. Like just like you
can never convince an addict to stop
doing drugs. It has to come from within.
You have to reach your own level of rock
bottom before you want to change.
So the people in there that are not
ready to change are not going to. The
people that are open and susceptible to
new information and new ideas, they they
love to listen to me talk. Like cuz even
when I was in there, I would still when
I reached my rock bottom and I did
recover my first day back in the pod,
like I instantly like instantly went to
meditation. I instantly went to yoga. I
instantly went to working out.
Everything that was no longer serving me
stopped from that moment on. There was
no more of it. Like I never touched a
drug from that day on.
>> And like I don't drink. I don't I don't
smoke cigarettes. I don't do nicotine. I
I literally do nothing. And and even
recently I quit smoking weed because I
felt that even that was at a stark
contrast for who I saw myself as. You
know, I I preach overcoming victim
mentality and sobriety and all this.
Like I can't be I can't be out there
smoking weed, you know, like I don't
judge people to do I don't judge people
that drink, you know, but if someone is
open to ideas and they're open to having
an open forum and a and a discussion on
how to better themselves, like I'm all
for it. Like I would love to help people
see a new perspective on life and that
news perspective can be offered through
my stories and my experiences because
I've lived it. Like I've lived life as a
drug dealer. I've lived life as, you
know, I've been on high-speed chases, on
crotch rockets. I've done like all the
crazy stuff that you can imagine. I'
I've probably done it. Like, I've I was
involved in a murder in Washington. Like
I didn't kill anybody, but I was
involved in a murder in Washington state
where I helped move a body and helped
someone potentially almost escape murder
charges, you know, like and that was all
due to the psychology of the mind, you
know, when I was at a lower level
of lower level of intellect and a lower
psychological point and a lower
energetic state like I was surrounding
myself with these things. and what you
surround yourself with multiplies.
>> So, I'm like I said, I'm just grateful
every day for my mindset, you know,
grateful that I I hit my rock bottom.
I'm grateful that I'm still here.
>> Yeah, bro. Well, I'm I'm grateful that,
you know, from your rock bottom, it
really it really snapped you into the,
you know, the the light within you. Kind
of took control of the steering wheel,
right? Um what what I was curious about
um is
so I in prison I imagine there's books
and stuff right um what what were you
drawn to? Who were you reading? What
were you listening can you listen to
YouTube at all or anything like that?
Were you listening to podcasts? Anything
like that?
>> Uh you can um I had a cell phone when I
was in prison. You're not supposed to
obviously but I had a cell phone my
whole time in there. is a touchcreen. So
I was like I was facetiming people every
once in a while on the street and I
would use it to mainly download like
movies and music and things like that.
And my main staple was I would download
meditation music and I would spend a lot
of time in my cell and I would just
meditate and that was my peace, you
know. And I went through a phase where
um I don't know if you're gonna put this
on the podcast, but I went through a
phase where I was on um I was having
someone ship me in um acid on birthday
cards and I would drop acid and I would
go meditate for like 6, eight hours and
I would literally reprogram myself
because I would find the pieces of my
internal self that were no longer
serving me. Hell yeah.
>> And I would just delete them like it was
a computer program. Like get that out of
here. get that out of here. I need to
bring this in. I need to adjust this,
you know, and I would just I would work
my mind over.
>> Okay. So, were you like what like what
drew you to do these things? Were these
just like instinctual kind of like have
you always been into like meditation and
yoga and that sort of stuff or
psychedelics?
>> Um, yes and no. Um, I was I was always
very spiritual growing up. Um, ever
since I was little, I had an uncanny
ability to see things like future
events, things that haven't happened. I
could see things that others couldn't. I
could feel energies and I just I knew
what was right and I knew what was wrong
when it came to my my cannon moment, the
moment that I died, you know, I knew
from that moment on what was right and
what was wrong. And it's like that
younger version of myself resurfaced and
was like, "Hey, bro, like you have the
ability of discernment. Use it." You
know? So from that moment on, I knew
what was serving me. So I started having
um I had one friend who he was he was on
the the run from America because he was
facing like international drug
trafficking charges and he was actually
sending me books while I was in prison.
And so he would send me books on um like
meditation, he would send me books on
yoga, ha yoga and um integral theory
like collegiate level books, you know,
>> sitting at Ken Wilbur in in prison is so
tight.
>> Yeah. So I was I was literally on a
different level when it came to talking
with people in there that like I said,
people wanted to fight me because of the
way that I spoke. Mhm. Mhm.
>> So, I just like I said, I just started
going down rabbit holes, man. And one
thing led to another and now I can't
stop. Like every like right now I'm
reading uh Talk Like Ted. It's a it's a
book that teaches you just how to speak
better like when it comes to public
forums. And like because that's my goal.
My goal is to get on stages. My goal is
to reach out and affect and help as many
people as possible. And maybe my story
and insight will prevent someone from
going down the same road.
>> Yeah. Yeah. From prison to purpose
indeed, my friend. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Um, man, that's that's that's
really what it takes. I think um I think
the
the awakening uh into the true self and
kind of the breaking of the you know, we
kind of see through the illusion of the
story. So Sam Harris, who's a
neuroscientist and meditation teacher
and all these other things, modern
philosopher, he has um in his meditation
teachings, he talks about this moment
when say you're like on the street and
you're walking past, you know, a
restaurant or something and it's all
glass, like big open glass and you're
looking in and you're like, you know,
you can see everybody eating and the in
the kitchen and you can see the whole
thing and you're kind of just watching
and then suddenly you can kind of become
aware of your own reflection, you know?
you can kind of like, oh, like it was
right there the whole time. I was just
looking right through my own reflection
the entire like I was
>> oh but now like both are there but I can
still kind of like see my reflect. You
know what I mean? Like everybody has an
experience, right?
>> Um and he and he
he kind of talks about that like that's
like kind of the moment that we very
quickly kind of overlook in meditation
where we're kind of like really trying
to rest in in the center of the self of
the like the non- tryinging like dude
you're fine. Just like it's right there.
Don't try to jump past it. like the
reflection is there just kind of rest in
it sort of thing. Um, and I think that
the awakening
that that moment where you can kind of
like snap out of it, there is definitely
a like a before and an after. For me,
it's like there before my experience
like that where I really like truly kind
of like snapped out of it, you know, my
version of my like kind of NDE or my,
you know, condundalini awakening, my
spiritual awakening, whatever it was
like really kind of the big moment. Um
there's like a before Jacob and an after
Jacob, you know what I mean?
>> Yeah.
>> And so I don't know. I think um I'm kind
of curious to ask you more about like
just awakening in general, you know?
Like what do you think it is like the
that this thing that we've gone through
the thing that more men and women seem
to be going through? Like we talk about
it on all these podcasts. There's like
this whole new age movement on the
internet. Like, and even outside of the
whole new age thing, there's there's
tons of people having condundalini and
spiritual awakenings.
>> What's up with it, man? Like, what what
do you think? Isn't it isn't it so sick,
dude? It's pretty cool, dude. Me and
Jordan talk about it all time, but yeah,
like I don't know. What do you think
about it, bro? Like, what's going on?
What do you think?
>> I think that right now the the world is
waking up. And to put it broadly and
more specifically, it's the the harmonic
resonance of Earth, the Schuman
resonance is reaching a point right now
where it's forcing people to wake up
because if you're an antenna, which we
we are, we're antennas, right? And we're
an antenna for frequencies, outside
frequencies. And that's why we're so
affected by other people like and
people, places, and things affect us.
Like when you go to a new place, you can
feel the energy of it. Well, the earth
as a whole has a resonance and it's
called the human resonance. And normally
it's like seven hertz or whatever it is.
Well, the human resonance lately has
been
through the roof. There's been crazy
energetic spikes. And these energetic
spikes force us to resonate at a
different frequency. So if we are
energetic beings, beings of light and
whatever you want to call us and
antennas, we pick up on these outside
energies and frequencies, then what do
you think is going to happen if all of a
sudden the the resonant frequency of
Earth is just through the roof, you
know? Like we're we have no choice but
to to resonate with it, you know? So
it's causing people to wake up at an
alarming rate.
>> Yeah. Dude, it literally makes me think
of like that's of course how
>> that's how like a new sense would be
born, right? Like the like, you know,
kind of the the third eye, so to say,
opening is kind of this ability to have
the meta perspective on the world, like
the real the truth of what's going on.
You know, you have this
>> view from above while you're living
within. You know, you're like, "Oh,
[__] Okay, life is a maze, but I could
see it. I I know it's a maze, so I I
can't be fooled." You know, it is like
this um I mean maybe it would make sense
that the human species would be
gaining a new a new sense like going in
a direction of expanding what they are.
You know, we we walked out of however
the hell it happened. We walked out of
water. We were fishies or whatever. We
were tadpoles or whatever and then we
became, you know, land dwelling
creatures and monkeys and here we are
having a podcast. You know, like we're
going in some direction, you know. It
see it seems to um it seems like the
togetherness is only true and we are
being sucked in. You know
>> I think I think that Christians have one
thing right and that is the second
coming of Christ. But I think it's
misinterpreted as like Jesus Christ the
person returning. But I believe the
second coming of Christ is Christ
consciousness. I don't believe like
Jesus himself is going to like come down
out of the sky or virgin birth again or
whatever the Bible says. I believe the
second coming of Christ is just that.
It's Christ consciousness that some
people call it 5D, some people call it
like a condundalini awakening, whatever
you want to call it, but it is what it
is and everyone is experiencing it. You
know, it's this worldwide phenomenon
where everyone is waking up. Like look
at geopolitically right now across the
entire world. You know, countries are
waking up to their evil corrupt
governments. People are waking up to the
corruption and you know, victim
mentality within themselves and like the
whole world is getting a software update
right now, you know.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Pretty much. I mean we're
we're operating on the same hardware and
our software has been being used against
us for you know various various amounts
of time and various reasons for you know
uh
billionaires and oligarchies and and all
these uh you know all these people who
can control us uh by using our biology
aka like making us feared so they can
kind of control what we think. Um but
our our like you said our not only our
UI but our software is upgrading like we
are we are learning more. We are
becoming smarter. we are like experienc
I think um Alan Wat or not Al Watson but
a Terrence McKenna again he talks about
uh in such a trippy way but how time is
speeding up in this weird way and it's
like it almost makes sense like our
individual perceptions as we grow and we
like I said go towards a certain
direction
the amount of stuff that can happen in a
single millisecond is more and more like
when I used to look at 360p on a TV I'm
taking in that many pixels But now with
a simple glance I take in 4K you know we
have all these different things all
these technologies that have added up to
where in this in one moment we are
devouring more you know um so time is
not only speeding up but we are
it's going in a direction you know and
and it's very interesting that we are a
species that seems to be like waking up
and becoming aware of its direction like
it's it's very profound that you and I
started we had some sort of edge
experience erience and we're like, whoa,
the self is an important thing to talk
about and teach people about, you know?
>> Yeah.
>> I don't know, man. It's just Isn't that
wild? Isn't it just crazy?
>> Yeah. It's nuts to think that, you know,
one second you're dead and the next
you're helping people not die.
>> Yeah, that's good, man. We're all just
walking each other home after all.
>> Yeah, just walking each other home, man.
>> We're just like taking like Yeah, just
into the spirit realm. Like, yeah, I'll
meet you up there, bro. But I'm like,
I'm at work, you know. Uh uh man. Okay.
Um Okay, so I had I had did have a
couple questions. Um
>> Okay, so you had a quote that I really I
thought was dope. Um I think this
happened right after your overdose
experience. Um can correct me if I'm
wrong, but you you said the version of
you that learned to stay hard so you
didn't break. Um,
>> so it seemed like you discovered that
you had made this armor and you needed
that for a certain time, but then you
became aware that that armor didn't
work. Is that correct? Is that kind of
what happened with you?
>> Yeah, exactly, man. Like you put on this
persona so that you don't get taken
advantage of, but in all reality, like
it's not even needed. Like a lot of
these identities that you wear are
identities that were given to you in the
first place. They're not self-inflicted
identities. It's like, you know, your
dad said you're good at football, so you
played football. Like I I never wanted
to play football, you know? I I did that
for him because he said [__] he liked
me playing football, you know? And you
know, it's a trickle down thing. You
know, each one of these identities and
labels are from outside sources or from
friends and family or whatever the
situation may be.
So yeah, staying hard is the quickest
way to never change.
Can you give me an example uh like uh in
in your personal life uh maybe not even
like in in the prison experience maybe
even before that
>> where you were living through your armor
um where where you were very knowingly
like a good example where someone go oh
like maybe I'm kind of living that kind
of sounds like something I would do like
where you walk into a room and you're
acting a certain way or you project a
certain image to protect yourself. Does
anything come to mind bro?
>> Yeah. Um, my entire life,
my entire life, I I held on this held on
to this persona of, you know, I was
always like, like when I was growing up,
I always was the protector when it came
to my little sisters, when it came to my
friends. Like I would always, you know,
beat up people that were in the wrong
because, you know, I was that was who I
was. But in all actuality, like maybe
those people didn't need beaten up, you
know, maybe they needed help, you know?
So, I was living through that armor,
living through that persona instead of
seeing the situation for what it was.
And like hurt people hurt people, man.
And the reason people lash out and they
get aggressive or they get violent is
just because they have internal healing
that needs to be done.
So
what is what does the future of this
whole healing journey look like for
you know all of us I guess like you know
we we have hospitals we have these
buildings these structures in our
societies that when you're hurt you go
to these hospitals and they need a lot
of work but it's you know they're they
have their greatness and they have they
have their good good aspects and you
know it's at least trying to solve a
problem right hey there's someone
bleeding let's get them like some clean
you know sanitary whatever
>> so So in that same direction you know we
have psychiatry we have you know we got
better help we got we got all these you
know mental health but um you know
>> I don't believe in psychiatry
>> I don't believe in psychiatry okay well
what what do we need in its place then
like what is how do how do we heal in
the future
>> I believe most healing can be done
energetically like
>> tell me
>> think about so our belief creates our
reality right
>> just like you know kind of A little
flashback here to the the double slit
experiment. The if our belief creates
our reality. So if something is outside
of your awareness, it is a wave. It no
longer exists on the physical plane.
Right? So in order for it to be
physical, you have to bring awareness to
it. And the same thing goes with
healing. It's it goes it's been studied
and proven that a positive mindset and
belief in a healing journey will heal
someone much faster than conventional
medicine.
Um uh have you ever looked into um like
breath work like Wimhof?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I did did breath work this
morning.
>> Perfect. So you know Wimhof um he sat
down and was injected with Ebola or
polio or some
>> dude. Yeah. This is so crazy. Please go
on.
>> So he was injected with some deadly
pathogen. Him and his team and under
medical observation using nothing but
breath work, mindset, and meditation, he
completely
combed this deadly pathogen. What?
Wasn't it like 24 hours? Like it was
some like ridiculous amount of time.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Dude, it's they
literally just have him hooked up to
neural neural caps and videos and he's
just being recorded the whole time and
he's actively fighting off this virus.
So it just changes what we know. Yeah.
Belief, bro. Belief. That's all it is.
Energy and frequency and matter and
everything is controlled with our
belief. Like if we are all God, then we
all have the powers of God as well. We
just have to tap into them. And these
these powers that we possess are slowly,
well, I won't even say slowly. It's kind
of a tidal wave at this moment. Like
everyone's waking up like on a massive
morning.
>> Yeah. Like grand rising. Here you go.
Here's some telepathy,
you know.
>> Yeah. And I'm giving you telepathy
through my mind.
>> Yeah. Exactly. You know, we're all
waking up to the fact that we all are
gods. We are in the Bible. It even says
ye are gods. It doesn't say ye are like
gods.
>> It says ye are gods
>> because we're all a fractal of the one
true God. The all that is, the universe,
the, you know, collective consciousness,
whatever you want to call it. You know,
something dude that I that I find,
it's again, it's kind of me going back
to that example that I was talking about
with Sam Harris where he talks about
where he's looking through the
restaurant and suddenly can see his
reflection. You know, it's like the
inside of the restaurant and the
reflection, it's all right there at the
same time. Sometimes I think that unless
you've had that experience, like a
genuine at least that glimpse of like
kind of the true nature of just like
consciousness in a Okay, I know that's
like such a loaded sentence, but just
to, you know, not ramble about it too
much,
unless we've had that when you and I are
talking about like victim mindset and
like um getting lost in your stories and
um you know, we are all gods like that
sort of stuff because like I use a lot
of the same language as you.
Do you think that people really are
hearing what they should be hearing or
can they hear us if they haven't had
that like awakening? What what is do you
think?
>> So Ken Wilbur actually talks about this.
Okay.
>> There are there's levels of
consciousness.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And
it's easy for someone like me and you to
talk to somebody at a lower level of
consciousness. And I'm not saying
intellect. I'm saying consciousness.
>> And it's easy for us to talk someone at
a lower level of consciousness. and
understand their perspective,
but they will never understand ours
until they live through it.
>> Yeah. It's like a It's like an elevator.
>> Mhm.
>> And like until you get up to that next
floor, you can't understand the
perspective like the,
>> you know, the 2D to 3D perspective of
that whole floor.
>> Exactly. But to add to that, think about
if you're if you're like driving over to
my house right now and I give you
um the address, but you don't use Google
Maps or navigate or anything like that.
It's going to take you a while to get
here. Like you know what you know where
I live, but it's going to take you a
while to get here. But if I give you a
map, the same thing with consciousness.
If I give you a map of consciousness
now, you're going to understand like how
to get there because you understand like
at least on a a basic level what
consciousness is, what that next level
is, where I'm going. But if you don't
know where you're going, how long is it
going to take you to get there,
>> right?
Yeah. A a a ship with no destination
favors no winds or or a sailboat with no
destination favors no winds. Like do I
need to go to the east or the west, you
know?
>> Yeah, exactly. I don't even know what
port I'm [__] going towards.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, yeah, there is like
Yeah, there needs there is a direction.
Yeah, that's so interesting.
So, how do we
so so how do how do dudes like you and
us who are like trying to help people
who are trying to share our perspectives
and just like you know express who we
are and what we've learned on the path
knowing that when people are ready
they'll come up for some air you know um
how do we communicate in a way that
doesn't feel like sometimes what happens
with like podcasting and stuff dude you
probably noticed it too uh it becomes
like
yay this and boo that, you know, like.
So, how do we make sure that we're not
going like, "Yay, if you're if you
identify with being all that is in God
consciousness, but if you think you're
just a small identity, like, yo, you
suck, dude." Like, you know what I mean?
Like, how do we not tribalize ourselves
when we're trying to help people? You
know, cuz I get I get tripped up and
like sometimes I'll hear myself back and
go, "Well, I I kind of worded that in a
way that like I could totally hear that
they would take that as me sounding like
I'm cooler or better. I know something
they don't or something, you So, how do
we navigate those waters, man?
>> Um, I think it starts with empathy. You
know, if you are empathetic in
everything that you do and understand
that the reason we're doing this is to,
you know, we're throwing people that
life raft that they need, you know. Um,
when you come from a place of purpose
and empathy, it doesn't come across that
way, you know. And if someone perceives
it that way, they're not ready. They're
not ready to hear the message, you know.
Yeah. Yeah, that's fair.
Yeah.
Okay.
How about this? Oh, you had a video. I'm
just glancing at my notes here for
anybody who's just listening. I'm
waiting on the pause.
>> You had a video um in explore where this
goes. I'm not expecting you to remember
exactly what you said in the video, but
you did have some excellent excellent
points. What are three things that
prison taught you?
three things that prison taught me. Um
well, empathy without standards creates
weak adults is one of the my main ones.
And kind of to elaborate on that is like
when you are empathetic, people in
victim mindset will easily attach
themselves to someone with a higher
empathy level and use that as a as a
leverage point. you know, like if you're
empathetic towards me and I can't afford
rent or something like that, you're
like, "Oh, I got you, bro. Here's some
money." Ding, ding, ding. You know, now
all of a sudden, the victim becomes um a
capitalist,
you know.
>> And another thing that prison taught me
is how to read people. Like, one of the
biggest things is reading people and
realizing that a smile is not a smile.
You know, just because somebody is
smiling does not mean they're your
friend.
>> And I'd say the third thing that prison
taught me is
you got to take care of yourself first.
You know, you can't you can't help
someone who's drowning if you're
drowning yourself.
>> All right, let's dig a little bit deeper
on that. I think that is a super
important one because people get caught
up in being the hero and saving the
world before they, you know, quote
unquote make their own bed. Um, the the
example of on an airplane if you're in
an emergency, the mask comes down. You
got to put your own oxygen mask on first
so you don't die before you start
helping the person next to you or your
daughter, your kid, whatever.
>> So,
>> I don't know. Tell me more about that.
>> So, you can't pour from an empty cup,
>> you know? So you have to fill your cup
first and whether that be through
meditation, breath work, uh identity
work, like you have to transform
yourself into a person that has the
ability to help in the first place. If
you are telling people, hey, don't eat
fast food. That shit's poison. But yet
here you are snacking on a Snickers.
Like who are you to be the the end all
be all and the justified party, you
know? So you have to put yourself in a
position where you can help in the first
place.
>> Be the person that you want other people
to be so that when you reach down and
you pull people up, they see like, "Oh,
it is nicer up here. You were right."
And it's not like you're telling people
like, "Oh, meditation is so great. Like
I feel so great for meditation." But
really low-key, you don't even meditate.
You're just over there scrolling or
something. You know, you wake up at
every rise and you're just on your phone
scrolling or waking up and eating junk
food or whatever the case may be. You
got to take care of yourself before you
can take care of anybody else.
>> Yeah, absolutely. I feel like it's
definitely life is really a proof is in
the pudding type thing. Like you don't
get other people inspired to meditate by
Yeah. walking around saying I'm a
meditator and like you know clocking
your hours and sharing your stats on
social media. You know, it's like people
just you you meditate for your reasons
for because it's the way that you serve.
Um it's the way that you uh you know,
connect to what's larger than you within
you and your personal practice. And then
who you are proves itself in real
moments. You know, not to say that just
because you meditate you won't, you
know, get angry or have an outburst or,
you know, have a little road rage or or
whatever it is that you that you deal
with. But if there is someone who knows
you before you started meditating or and
they know you after you started
meditating, they may genuinely notice
like, "Hey man, you are way more chill
or you are way more understanding or you
are way more this or that." Um, you
know, the the proof proves itself and
you didn't even have to tell them. They
might even be like, "Yo, what are you
doing?" And then you could say, "Oh,
well, you know, I've been meditating.
It's pretty sick." But you don't you
don't walk around saying, "Well, I
meditate. I'm sick. Watch how sick and
calm I am. Watch watch how you know what
I mean?" Like it just
>> Yeah. Yeah. You don't Yeah. You don't go
to the mall to meditate so people can
watch you meditate and then they know
you're a meditator. It's like no, bro.
You do it for you and you know the the
the fruit is is bear uh by other people
just noticing that you're in a different
state.
>> Yeah. Exactly. Like when you talk to
when you talk to people, you have a
different air about you and people
people recognize that. Like if you talk
to people that just something something
as simple as meditation or changing your
diet, people notice that whether it's
consciously or subconsciously, there's
something different about you to the
normal, you know, uninitiated.
>> And when you when you talk to these
people, they're subconsciously inspired
by you. They don't know what it is. They
don't they they they feel it. They don't
know it. And it's palpable because like
we were saying earlier, levels of
consciousness. When someone's at a lower
level of of consciousness and they come
across somebody that is resonating at a
diff at a different frequency,
they feel it. Their antenna picks it up.
They don't know what it is, but it's
there.
>> Yeah. It's like it's like sensing It's
like sensing, yo, I have a I have a
plugin that would fit that thing you
have. Like I think I have that plugin in
me, you know, like like I think I have
like imagine if you were um like you
used to be Have you seen Avatar? Like
the blue people Avatar?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Imagine like you were one of those
and then throughout hundreds and
hundreds of years you like just stopped
using your little tail connector thing
and so you just became like this
creature that's blue and doesn't have a
tail connector thing, but then you saw
some other avatars who like took out
their tail and they connected it to like
the great mother ya or whatever it is in
avatar world. You'd be like, "Oh, what
what the what the fuck?" But then you'd
have to look at your own life and like
all the things you do that are anti that
tail thing and it might be triggering
and so you might oh I have to change all
of the sudden and so you either dive
deeper into the identity you are or you
go
>> let me what hey what's that tail thing
you're doing? Tell me about that. Like
how do I what is that? Do I have can I
do that? How do I do that? You know what
I mean?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm I'm curious and I I've
been told my whole life that it's you
know it's taboo but I kind of want to
try it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Well, dude. So, Ramdov says
like when he's talking these big
lectures,
he talks about how, you know, he could
be talking for an hour straight and
nobody's saying anything. People are in
a trance. They're just nodding their
heads. And then he's like,
>> he's like, "How do you how do you guys
know any of this? How are you just
nodding your heads like, "Oh yeah, that
is how it is." Ohh. Oh, yeah. And he's
talking these deep spiritual concepts
and he's talking about his self-dying
and and all the psych psychological
stuff. And everyone in the audience is a
yeah that is yes Ramdas that is how it
is you know it is how it is and it's
like how do you know that how do you
know that and it's like they couldn't
reverberate they couldn't tell you
exactly what he's saying you know maybe
in some way they could but it's it's
this thing within you it's this shape of
something larger than yourself that you
have like a you know like I said the
plugin it'll fit just fine it'll fit
like a puzzle piece you have that shape
of it in you it's just life is trying to
hand the experiences to, you know, plug
in, to turn in, to to to tune in to drop
out, as Timothy Larry would say.
>> I love Timothy Larry. You know, I
actually knew his niece.
>> No way.
>> No. Kn know his niece. Yeah.
>> Whoa. Okay. What's that like? What's
that like relationship like? Has she
told you any stories about him or
anything?
>> Uh, not too many stories. Um, it was in
it was before my uh overdose experience
in prison, so it was a different version
of me that knew.
And because of that, I was meeting her
for different reasons. You know, I was
dropping things off. And
>> she's actually a pot grower um in Bend,
Oregon. She's like one of the largest
pot growers actually. Um yeah, like
thousands of plants kind of thing. Um
>> Timothy would be proud.
>> Yeah. Yeah. He's smiling in his grave
right now, you know. But she was cool.
She was uh for someone that grew a lot
of weed, she was very hyper. Um but she
was super sweet. She was, you know,
little small stature person. Like super
nice though. She lives in Portland,
actually.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Interesting.
>> Right off Yeah. Right off Rosa Parks.
>> Oh, nice, dude. Yeah. Hey, dude. You
wonder if there's like some, you know,
the lineage thing is is pretty
interesting. Like I don't dive too deep
into my personal lineage. I don't really
know a ton about it, but it is kind of
interesting when,
>> you know, the the descendants of some
known figure stumble into similar areas,
you know, like I wouldn't say that, you
know, being a a I'm sure she knows her
stuff with with pot if she's like one of
the biggest pot growers. So, that's
pretty cool that she comes from the, you
know, the background of Timothy Larry
being in her family.
>> Yeah. Here's a a crazy uh a loop, a
crazy loop of connection. So Timothy
Liry back in the day was friends with uh
Nicholas Sans. Nicholas Sans um was
friends with a guy named Sasha Scholan,
Alexander Scholan. He was he wrote a
book called PCAL. It stands for
phenylmines I've known and loved. And it
was pretty much a book on chemical
compositions of finephomines like LSD
and 25i and 25e and all the derivatives
and things like that. Well, while I was
in prison the first time, I met somebody
who studied how to cook underneath
um Alexander Sasha Schulen, right? And
then one thing led to another. I get out
of prison and I started cooking uh Molly
with the same person. So I was actually
cooking Molly with someone who learned
how to cook Molly from the godfather of
acid who is friends with Timothy Liry
who I met his niece or whatever. So I
was like and this is all in different
Yeah. And this is all over the the
country. This isn't all in one small
area. This is like in Washington,
Oregon, California, Tennessee. Like like
I was all over the place and I just
happened to meet this like hive of
people that were all connected back in
the day and connected now still.
Man, where do you where do you put that
in your brain? Where do you
compartmentalize it? Like I know like
synchronicities are an impossible thing
to explain, but like the coincidences
seem to add up in certain things. Like
do you think like maybe like I knew
these people in a past life somehow?
Maybe like I don't know how do you
conceptualize that sort of stuff,
>> man? I don't even know where to start on
that. Like it's it's so crazy sometimes
like like realistically if we started
talking long enough I bet you we met at
some point in time or our parents did or
maybe like
>> 20 years ago there's a picture of us at
Wild Waves, you know, where you were in
the background of a family photo, you
know, like
>> we're all connected, bro. We are all
God.
>> Yeah. Yeah, dude. That that stuff is
something else. That is
>> Yes. I was actually just listening to
Ram Das.
It was either last night or this
morning. Um, and he was talking about
this dude was talking about
synchronicities and the guy was like,
"No, like something's going on like
that." Like they're really getting more
and more. And Ron Das is basically
saying like your perspective is
expanding. That's what going on. Like
synchronicities are literally always
happening. It's just sometimes certain
moments in your life you get to kind of
like have that meta perspective where
you notice that they're all happening.
But like realistically, if you had the
ability to in the click of a finger
always zoom all the way out, you would
go, "Oh, like there's a it's all
synchronicities. Everything is literally
all connected." Like everything at all
points is never not been connected. But
um yeah, so it's not necessarily like
new synchronicities start happening. It
is almost like a your ability to be
aware of them um kind of like expands
and like breathes a little bit, you
know?
>> Yeah, I feel that 100% man. Like there
is points in time when I get deep into
meditation that I feel and see not like
with my eyes but I see the invisible
thread that connects like everything and
that's when the connections feel
palpable more than synchronistic
but other than that like it's like when
I'm not meditating when I'm not in those
transcendental states it's just like
what the [__] you know it's like how is
all this happening simultaneously or how
is this connected to this or how do I
speak something and then it instantly
happened, you know?
>> Mhm. Yeah. I mean, there's more and more
research being done on a lot of that
stuff. Uh what's his name?
Uh he talks about like the uh he did
this study, man. Who is it basically? He
he studied animals, animals behavior. So
like animals being able to basically
sense when their um adults are coming
home, when their owners are coming home.
And he would do it different times a
day. Okay. So, it's not just like, oh,
they know about 5:00 p.m. is when, you
know, mom and dad comes home. They do
different cars, so they don't just
recognize their car from down the road.
There's like all these crazy studies.
Um, I'm still forgetting the guy's name,
but um Oh, Rupert Sheldrake, I think.
Rupert Spira, Rupert,
>> I think it's Rupert Sheldrake. But, uh,
yeah. So, I mean, he talks about these
like these abilities, these like
knowings, these like things that you can
kind of get in tune with. And like even
our animals have these like senses,
these abilities that they can get in
tune with. And I think like even
synchronicity is something like it's
almost like a little positive cookie
that like, oh, you're doing the thing,
like you're you're connected to the
thing, you're on the right path, you're
you know, it's a it's just like another
expansion of of an ability, you know.
>> And to take it a step further, like
there's a study that was conducted with
not only animal like your animals, but
they did it with plants. And your plants
have an energetic spike when you're on
your way home. When you're within like a
one or two mile radius.
>> What?
>> Yeah, plants.
>> Dude, oh, you know, and another crazy
one I heard about plants is uh there's a
book, The Light Eaters, that's pretty
good that I'm slowly picking my way
through. If you we studied that if you
put a Bluetooth speaker a speaker that's
playing the sounds of running water
underground that a a plant I don't know
if it's a specific kind of plants or all
but their roots will somehow hear here
hear that water and the roots will go
grow towards the sound of that running
water through the speaker
>> like going the other way.
>> Yeah. Like but like what you know like
it doesn't have sense organs as we
understand them. doesn't have ears and
and you know reverberating uh you know
>> like mechanics of an ear that we think
hearing only exists for this you know um
how fascinating is that like what we're
just discovering more and more about
this this whole thing we're living in
here. Yeah, we're just brushing the
surface, man. I mean, all the uh the
pseudocience that's out there is just
that, you know, it's people like even
the fallacy of math, like what is math?
Numbers are just [__] energetic
frequencies, too, you know? Like
everything is everything is energy at
its base, you know? So, we're all
connected. Everything is just under
living under one consciousness and we're
just now starting to scratch the surface
on what consciousness even is. Mhm.
Yeah. And what a tragedy to forget that.
You know what I mean? Like
>> Yeah.
>> Like and and what a blessing to remember
it.
>> Yeah. That's the beauty of it, you know,
like they say that you decide your
journey before you're incarnated, you
know, and who would want to incarnate
where you already know everything, you
know, like the the beauty of life is
discovering life itself.
>> Okay. Hey man, we're getting up here in
time, but I want to use what you just
said as like a um starting our journey
towards home here.
You just pointed out something that I
use in my life to never be a victim. And
that is the way I see it.
>> I signed up for all this [__]
>> I made these plans. me and God or me as
God or something, me and my spirit
family, whatever the hell happened
before I slow slid down the slide into
this human life as Jacob. I mapped it
all out and I said, I want to grow in
this way. I want to learn this so I can
teach people this. I want to experience
this tragedy so at this age I can heal
from it and at this age I can help other
people and I want to experience this and
expand and all these things. I planned
it all out and then I slid through onto
this magic big slide and I had to forget
that I planned any of that out because
it just wouldn't work if I remembered
any of it at all. You know, I had to
forget and here I am. And I use that and
I don't know if it's capital T true, but
I live as if it's true because I don't
know any other way to keep moving
forward and I don't know any other way
to explain this hunger that I have and
that you have this thing that keeps me
going. Um, so I figure I I signed up for
all of it. Uh, I imagine you live in
some sort of way that's similar. Um,
could you kind of explain your version
of that so anybody listening can maybe
give a different perspective on this
whole like past life quote unquote thing
or this like you know planning out your
life before you live it thing?
>> Yeah, definitely, man. So, I kind of
have the the inkling that our purpose is
predetermined so that when we do come
down here, we we already know what we're
going to do and how we're going to do
it, but it would lose its luster if we
already knew everything. So, that we we
come down here and everyone gets amnesia
and throughout life we're just battling
Alzheimer's essentially, you know,
trying to figure out everything like
what am I supposed to do now? And the
the ups and downs is what adds
excitement. And the the tumultuous
the tumultuous sides of life make the
calm parts, you know, a blessing and and
vice versa. Just like that the old
Persian adage where he asked somebody to
um make him a ring that said something
that when he was sad would make him
smile and then when he was happy it
would make him sad. So this ring bearer
came to him with a ring that said this
too shall pass, you know, and it's it's
perfect. Like it doesn't matter what
situation you're in, whether it be bad
or good, like it'll pass,
>> you know? So you just got to take it for
what it is, you know? Take it on the
chin if that's where it hits and just
keep going and realize that life is
exactly that. It's life. And without
purpose,
there's no point in it.
And we're here to give it that purpose.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Amen to that, bro. Hey, well
well said, dude. Thank you for Thank you
for taking my rambling like, you know,
side quest filled with plenty caveat
questions and uh always coming up with
like such a great roundabout way of uh
of explaining like your your version of
it or or answer my questions, man. You
have some great answers.
>> I appreciate it, man. This has been fun.
>> Yeah, absolutely, bro. Okay. Okay. Well,
so let's uh let's let's tie a bow on
this thing. What what message would you
like to leave? Is there any like scroll
through our conversation? Is there
anything that maybe you wanted to hit on
that you want to just take a few more
minutes on? Um and then I also just I
would love to know I'd love for you to
share what's in the future for you. What
what are you offering? Um where can
people find you? I'll obviously include
all the bio and like your links and all
that sort of stuff below, but uh what
can we expect? And uh scan your brain if
there's anything else you want to leave
left unsaid.
Well, that is a loaded question because
there's a lot that I would we could be
here for hours,
but uh to wrap it up, man, I'd just like
to say first off, thank you for having
me on, you know, I really appreciate the
opportunity and this is just a stepping
stone, you know, and I've been
manifesting this for, you know, a couple
of months now. I've been saying like I I
need to get a public forum. I want to
get on stages. I want to offer people
perspectives. I want to, you know, share
my story and like all these things. And
it's just crazy to think that because I
put that out there energetically,
vocally, and spiritually, like it's
happening. So my message would be to the
people listening, man, like if you have
a dream, if you have a vision, if you
have a higher calling, then just [__]
chase it. Like there's no nobody's going
to chase it for you. No, nobody's going
to pursue your passions like you are.
So, just get after it.
>> Bravo. Yeah, I agree, man. Yeah, there's
only uh there's only one you. There's
only one person that's filled with the
thoughts that you have. Like, it's
they're coming to you, man. Like, if
there's something that you want to be,
>> get after it. I agree. Oh, man. All
right. Well, hey, that was amazing, man.
Thank you so much for your time. Again,
listeners, if you're still listening, uh
check out all of Mr. Trey's info down
below. follow him on Instagram and all
those things. Be prepared for what's
coming next. Uh if you enjoyed it,
please share it with a friend. If you
liked it, maybe leave a little comment
and a positive review. Please follow
Trey. And what do I always say at the
end of every episode if anybody ever
gets this far is if you haven't drank
any water today. What's wrong with you,
dude? Drink some water, some spring
water at that. I know I'm over here
drinking my plastic bottle. Uh it's it's
it's time. It happens sometimes, but uh
any water is better than absolutely no
water, I would say, unless it's full of
bacteria from the Amazon rainforest.
Also, stretch, guys. Love your body,
love yourself, take some time to ask
yourself about your identity, and um we
will see you next episode. Much love,
Trey. Thanks one more time, brother.
>> Yeah,
>> thank you.
>> Namaste. The light in me season honors.
The light in you.
>> Cheers to the Junkyard Love podcast.
At what age do we learn how to have
better conversations?
At what age do we learn to have better
conversations with ourselves?
Knowledge is power.
Reality is